Privacy Policy
==============

Columbia Distributing (**“Columbia Distributing”** or **“We”**) respects your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website coldist.com (our “**Website**“) or use our The Fridge app (collectively, the “**Services**”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

* Through the Services.
* In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and the Services.
* Through mobile and desktop applications you download from the Servicers, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and the Services
* When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

* Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Columbia Distributing or any third party;
* Any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or through the Services.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Services. By accessing or using the Services, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of the Services after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

Children Under the Age of 21

Our Services are not intended for people under 21 years of age. No one under age 21 may provide any personal information to the Services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from people under 21. If you are under 21, do not use or provide any information through the Services. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a individual under 21, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a person under the age of 21, please contact us at customer.service@coldist.com.

Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Services, including information:

* By which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“**personal information**“);
* That is about you but individually does not identify you, such as IP address, company affiliation, and Services usage, and/or
* About your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Services, and usage details.

We collect this information:

* Directly from you when you provide it to us.
* Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.
* From third parties, for example, our business partners.

**_Information You Provide to Us_**

The information we collect on or through our Services may include:

* Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Services.
* Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
* Details of transactions you carry out through our Services and of the fulfillment of your orders.
* Your search queries on the Services.

**_Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies_** 

As you navigate through and interact with our Services, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

* Details of your use of the Services, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use through the Services.
* Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, device information, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Services and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

* Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
* Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Services according to your individual interests.
* Speed up your searches.
* Recognize you when you return to our Services.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

* **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
* **Google Analytics.** We use a tool called “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of our Services. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit or use the Services, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to the Services. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve the Services. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit the Services, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you use the Services, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visit to or use of the Services is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to the Services by disabling cookies on your browser.

How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

* To present our Services and its contents to you.
* To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
* To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
* To provide you with notices about your account.
* To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
* To notify you about changes to our Services or any products or services we offer or provide though them.
* To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Services.
* In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
* For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and our affiliates’ goods and services that may be of interest to you.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

* To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
* To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.
* To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Columbia Distributing, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Columbia Distributing about our Services users is among the assets transferred.
* To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
* For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
* With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

* To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
* To enforce or apply [our terms of use](https://www.coldist.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/Terms-of-Use_July-2021.pdf) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
* If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Columbia Distributing, our customers, or others.

Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

* **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
* **Promotional Offers from Columbia Distributing.** If you do not wish to have your contact information used by Columbia Distributing to promote our own or our affiliates’ products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to service@coldist.com. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions.

Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Services and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an email at customer.service@coldist.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

State Specific Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, California law may provide you with additional rights regarding our use of your personal information. To learn more about your California privacy rights, [CLICK HERE.](https://www.coldist.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/CCPA-Notice_July-27.pdf)

Nevada residents who wish to exercise their sale opt-out rights under Nevada Revised Statutes Chapter 603A may submit a request to this designated address: customer.service@coldist.com. However, please know we **DO NOT** currently sell data triggering that statute’s opt-out requirements.

Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Services. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained in the Services.

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page or application home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Services and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

customer.service@coldist.com

**Customer Service**  
(888) 417-5001

[Privacy Policy](https://www.coldist.com/privacy-policy) | [Site Map](https://www.coldist.com/site-map) | [Legal](https://www.coldist.com/legal) | 2024 Columbia Distributing. All Rights Reserved.
